I love it so much. I love it so much. I love it so much.
I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love, I love.
Can we stop here?
No! No! No! No!
Rios has to let me in!
No! No! No! No! No!
No! No! No! No! No! No!
I just love you so much.
I like you so much.
I don't know what's going on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Promise me.
Yes. Tell me you love me.
You have to give me love all the time, all the time. No, no, no, no, no.
Please spoil me.
My heart is pounding. My heart is pounding.
I'm a little nervous. For you.
Released on Wednesday of this year, our music festival
With all of you here today.
Don't make me say a word.
Just look at me.
Cute, cute, cute, cute, I love you.
Pretty, pretty, pretty, pretty, kiss kisses for all of it.
It's not all fun and games.
It's a finite life.
It's a world full of mistakes.
It's all up to you.
♪ It's Mickey's story that's about to begin ♪
Let's go over that mountain
Hi-ho!Hi-ho.
Hey, you.
Near
Zero Distance
Closest
Like this.
I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much, I love you so much
I love, love, love, love, love.
Smabri.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
On the contrary, you can't come here for school because of your work,
I'm here all the time because I'm having fun.
Good morning.
Don't play with me.
What?
This way?
Huh?
Huh?What?
Don't fool around with me.
I'm trying to be nice.
All eyes on you.
You never know when they'll come.
Oh!
I'm kind of nervous about when it's coming
Scary, scary
I'm really scared.
The camera.
Oh!
Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr!
On!
Ong!
Kanami!
Churia!
Hitoka!
Maruko!
Aki!
Hiari!
Then, Tokimeki Advertising Department
Dock on!
It's got to be this one.
You're always stepping on my lap.
Please spoil me some more.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, noDon't look at me sideways.
I'm the only one you should be looking at.
My heart is pounding.
I'm so excited... for you.
I'm so excited for you.
Speaking of which...
Hi, I'm Hiyori Yoshikawa a.k.a. Hiyori-n. I'm Hiyori Yoshikawa, aka Hiyorin.
I'm Hiyori, Hiyori Yoshikawa, a.k.a. Hiyori Nori.
I'm sure you all know this already, but for those of you here at 180 degrees above.
Our name is "Cho-Tokiimeki Advertising Department".
I hope you will search for us and take a good look at our cute faces.
I would like you to take a good look at our cute faces.
I hope you will like us today.
I look forward to working with you.
Hiyorin Hiyorin
I hope you like her.
So today is the release day of "Cute Memorial".
So we're going to have a rock opening time.
Yay!
Please pray a lot.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
What? What?
What?
Okay, everyone in front of the store there.
I love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love, love.
I love, love, love, love, love, love.I love, love, love it.
Kawaii Kawaii Kawaii! It's too much!
Kawaii Kawaii, your smile
On your body
One, two, three, four!
Even though the days go on and on
I'll never change my mind
I'm here for you
I'm bursting
I feel like I'm about to burst... more and more...
I can't catch up with you
Someday we'll be together
I just thought I heard a song I know.
I'm wondering if some of you might have stopped to listen to the song I know.
I hope all of you who live in Kanagawa will come to see me!
I'll be waiting for you!
Come on!
Rock on to your hearts!
That's all for us, the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department!
Thank you very much!
Have a good day, and please come back and see us again.
Today was our first free live performance in a while, and there were many nostalgic moments,
It was a very enjoyable time.
I will be back again at Yokomai in Kanagawa,
We will be back again at Yokoumi, so we will continue to do our best to show everyone how we have grown,
We will continue to do our best so that we can show you how we have grown,
I hope you will all continue to follow us.
Thank you very much for your support today.
I would like to thank all of you who have always supported us,
I would be very happy if you could come and see the show, no matter who you are or what kind of people you are.I hope everyone, no matter who you are, will come to see us.
We will give our best performance,
Please come.
So, thank you very much for coming to the release event of "Cute Memorial" today,
Thank you very much.
Now, let's rock on to your hearts!
That's all for us, the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye!
See you soon!
That was awesome!
So much fun!
Oh, that looks so good!
Toki ices!
Looks delicious!
Today, we had a free live show with Saru-san's guests.
Yay! It was fun!
So much fun!
The students were amazing,
Some of them came to see the show without leaving the venue,
It was a celebration.
It was a celebration, and it was a weekday, too,
Please come to our booth.
Thank you very much!
I want to do it again!
It's fun, isn't it?
Sometimes, it's like a taste change,
I hope we can do free live shows again.I'm hoping to do free live shows again.
Yes, I am,
May there be more people who are a little bit more super-patient!
Please!
Great, at the building.
From the point of view of so many penlights already.
It was amazing,
There were also a lot of people on the 2nd and 4th floors,
It was a very fun experience!
It was a very enjoyable experience!
I think there were a lot of people who saw the show for the first time,
I hope this will be a good opportunity for us to have many more
I was thinking that it would be great if we could have many more members of the advertising department
I was thinking how happy I would be
I was performing!
Right, Aki-chan, it's your first time, isn't it?
That's right! It was my first time to do a live performance like this.
I was so happy to be able to perform in this way,
I was so excited.
I was so excited,
It was so much more fun than I had imagined.
I had a lot of fun,
It was a great summer memory for me.
I have good memories of the summer release!
I was also able to have a release event close to the release date.
I was able to have a release event close to the release date,
I hope this will be a good opportunity to spread more cute memorials!
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best!Let's go for it!
Just remember the name of the advertising department on the plane!
Remember me!
And please dance on TikTok!
Some people might be watching!
Of course!
You might not be at home in a different place!
Please dance on TikTok too!
Please do!
Bye bye!
It's amazing to do it in this shopping mall
It's great to be here!
It's been so long!
I feel like I'm walking out of a store,
I was like, "What's up with those girls? The way they look at me, the way they look at me.
I've been looking at them from a different angle,
It's been so long since I've seen the new place.
I was so excited!
I was a little nervous when I was skiing!
When we were skiing,
When I was skiing, a bunch of high school kids were walking by to watch me.
I was really curious.
And then at the end, they were looking at me like this.
It was funny!
I thought it would be good for my confidence
I felt like it gave me a lot of confidence.
I'd like to do it again.
I want to do it again! So much!
A lot!So many!
Even though it was a weekday!
Thank you all for coming!
Thank you very much!
I'd like to have a re-leave once a month!
For sure!
Thank you very much!
Goodbye goodbye, thank you for yesterday
After the rain, the streets are turning colors
And on the canvas of my broken heart, I paint a piece of the future
And lead us on the way.
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
I'll remember.
When it's raining
I'll try to make you laugh
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye
To me yesterday
After the rain, the streets sparkle
as if my heart is in a sunny mood
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, then goodbye
Then goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a flower, I'll let you play with my tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
Goodbye then, to yesterday's meThen goodbye to yesterday's me.
Please subscribe to our channel!